UJWALA SHINDE

Digital Marketing Manager

uiwala.sawat@gmail.com 9082493782 Pune, India

SUMMARY

Seasoned digital marketer with 8+ years' experience in building and implementing strategies focused on SEO, Social media, email marketing, and AdWords. Successfully grew organic revenue by 25% in 8 months through a content creation and build up strategy. Holding Team management experience which includes Performance management, KPI, KRI, Goal setting.

EXPERIENCE

Associate Digital Marketing Manager

06/2023 to ongoing

Dess Technologies

- Effectively strategizing and executing digital marketing campaigns, emphasizing SEO/SEM, boosting organic traffic, utilizing email marketing, social media, and implementing adwords marketing for success.
- Working on B2B Saas Software to get more leads through data research and

Digital Marketing Manager

01/2022 - 06/2023

Zee lean - MT Educare

Mumbai

- Established in-house knowledge of marketing content leveraged this to incrementally improve customer LTV by 28%
- Strategized developed and managed paid digital marketing across adwords, instagram, facebook with monthly budget 1L per month
- Launched SEO strategy with highlighting long tail keywords and voice search SEO whichhelps to increase organic traffic by 30%
- Created report of SEO and paid marketing funnels, and helps to improve way forward strategy

Digital Marketing Manager

09/2018 -12/2021

Personalfn-Quantum information pvt Ltd

- Strategic planning and successful implementation of digital marketing Campaigns with focus on SEO/SEM, increased organic traffic ,email marketing, social media and adwords marketing
- Successfully increased website traffic by 50% and sales by 35% over a 10-month period by focusing on optimizing the user experience and creating efficient
- Analyzing and learning from the success and failures of various campaigns, and nurturing strong analytical ability to evaluate end-to- end customer experience across multiple channels and customer touch points
- Identifying trends, insights, and brainstorming with internal teams on creating new and unique growth strategies to drive sales
- Maintaining and increasing social media presence across all digital channels to generate high traffic and sales for the company.

Digital Marketing Executive

08/2015 -08/2018

Urja Communications

- Schedule, Optimize and report all social media campaigns and engage with users throughgiveaways and event promotions to grow combined followers by 3X
- Performed through marketing research and competitive analysis to understand effectively communicate product value proposition
- Provided recommendations and executed strategies for content development in relationto keyword specific seo goals
- Worked with SEO tea on projects invlving on site and off site optimization, positioning and the analysis of the results.
- Completion of technical seo for more than 10 brands.
- Excellent knowledge of collaborating with both internal and external sources to strategizesocial media content



TRAINING / COURSES

Universal Adversting Successfully completed Search Engine Optimization (SEO) and Social Media Optimization (SMO), Pay Per Click (PPC)

PROUD OF

Musafir.com

Dubai Visa keyword rank on google 1st position with compete with dubaivisa.net website which helps to increase organic visitors and leads

PersonalFN

Increased traffic by 50% in Personalfn to rank high competitive

MT Educare

Received employee of month award due to good performance

Skills

- SEO/ Search engine Optimization
- Semrush, Ahref, Screaming frog
- CRM leadsquared, Zoho
- Competitor Analysis & Keyword Research
- Google Adwords/ Ads
- Paid Marketing Facebook, Instagram, Linkedin
- Google Analytics, GA4
- Strategic Planning
- Client Handling
- Team Management
- Agency Management
- E-Commerce Marketing
- Performance Marketing
- Vend or Management Project Management
- SEO On Page & Off Page
- Google Data Studio Photoshop
- Illustrator
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript

EXPERIENCE

SEO Executive 03/2015 - 03/2015

Musafir.com Mumbai

- Develop SEO strategies, and implement and monitor strategies result
- Perform site analysis, keyword research and mapping, and assess link building opportunities
- Perform competitor SEO research
- Based on analysis, results and feedback, continually improve and modify strategies tooptimize effectiveness
- Prepare analytics and ranking reports for management
- Suggested keywords & URL structure for every new pages
- Maintain maximum effectiveness while adhering to strict deadlines and budgets Keep up-to-date with constantly changing technological and search engine trends, algorithms and ranking factors

SEO Executive 12/2013 – 03/2015

Alpha Overseas International Pvt

- Performed competitor research using free tools woorank, ahref.
- Developed the Seo plan for clients, and Implement and monitor the ranking report.
- Seo on page optimization
- Keyword Research for client website.
- Handling Google webmaster tool and analysis the factors of Planning and implementingpowerful link building strategies to increase each client's link popularity and gain visibilityon major search engines
- Developed the social media strategies and optimization
- Suggesting additional content optimization strategies for clients in areas such as blogs.

EDUCATION

MSC. IT 2014

Mumbai University

BSC.IT 2011

Mumbai University

STRENGTHS

Driving inbound track

Lead generation and increased traffic via SEO, SEM, Adwords, Data analysis, email marketing, social selling are my strengths

Increasing revenue

Bottom Line is very important to my success and with every organization, I have tried to work on 10x levels.

Ability to adapt, Creativity & Independence

Change is a constant part of the digital Marketing universe and my creativity, curiosity and Independent decision making helps me embrace the fast pace of digital marketing at every turn